[{"answer": "You're pretty focused.", "docId": "120107pmt", "aSentId": 14, "question": "And just for the hell of it, how I'm doing?", "qSentId": 13}, {"answer": "I don't Tweet.", "docId": "120107pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "Very good.", "docId": "120107pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "How does that make you feel?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "120107pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "So you didn't repeat very often?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "Well, you know, it's hard for me to -- I don't want to criticize them because I took a lot of heat.", "docId": "120107pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "What do you think about the way that television has evolved since your daily show stopped?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "ONAHUE: Well, it wasn't my idea.", "docId": "120107pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "Would you like that to be your epitaph, Phil?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "120107pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "That it would be strange if you did approve of it all in a sense, wouldn't it?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "Everybody thought their kids would catch it if they watched it.", "docId": "120107pmt", "aSentId": 109, "question": "What was the reaction to that?", "qSentId": 108}, {"answer": "We had a very good program with Mohamed Ali.", "docId": "120107pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "If I could I let you do one again tomorrow, what would it be?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "120107pmt", "aSentId": 123, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 122}, {"answer": "Marlo did a book titled \"The Right Words, At The Right Time\".", "docId": "120107pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "Which you just don't get that package, do you, very often?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "Completely.", "docId": "120107pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "Each also brought pride and boldness to young black males, you know?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "And one of many.", "docId": "120107pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "What do you have make of the Rick Santorum surge?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "120107pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "Guantanamo, you mean?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "He's calling for a nanny government.", "docId": "120107pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "And this is an abject, miserable failure that he should be lambasted for?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "Nobody runs around saying I'm a liberal, I'm a liberal.", "docId": "120107pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "What have you become?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "It was certainly true.", "docId": "120107pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "When you look back, what do you think?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "She didn't do too badly, but.", "docId": "120107pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "What did I say?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "I think Oprah has risen to a level in the stratosphere unknown to all of us.", "docId": "120107pmt", "aSentId": 365, "question": "What do you think of Oprah?", "qSentId": 364}, {"answer": "Well, I think she's - she's a compelling personality.", "docId": "120107pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "Why do you think?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "Well -", "docId": "120107pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "Is it the same?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "Look at my own early history.", "docId": "120107pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120107pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "I mean that's a pretty good endorsement, isn't it?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "He's going to break through that barrier I hope and believe in a couple days in New Hampshire.", "docId": "120107pmt", "aSentId": 483, "question": "I suppose the one big unanswered question is why can he not break through this kind of what is becoming almost mythical 25 percent barrier of support in his own party?", "qSentId": 482}, {"answer": "I don't think we'll ever get over it.", "docId": "120107pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "How has it been for you?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "I was thinking it was a nightmare and I was going to wake up.", "docId": "120107pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "Gabrielle Giffords has been shot, presumed dead and other people have been gunned down, what were you thinking when this was all unfurling?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120107pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "I mean, you, I know John, you first discovered your daughter was dead, was told, did they get (INAUDIBLE) the person who did this?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "It definitely it.", "docId": "120107pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "And did it give you any kind of comfort that they had?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "It was very difficult.", "docId": "120107pmt", "aSentId": 565, "question": "Was it cathartic in any sense?", "qSentId": 564}, {"answer": "No, not for me.", "docId": "120107pmt", "aSentId": 569, "question": "Is it hard to reconcile your faith when something like this happens?", "qSentId": 568}, {"answer": "Well, we do feel that he was mentally disturbed.", "docId": "120107pmt", "aSentId": 588, "question": "Let's talk about the person that did this, Jared Loughner, what are your views of him?", "qSentId": 587}, {"answer": "They go to christinataylorgreen.org and we have a web site.", "docId": "120107pmt", "aSentId": 614, "question": "And if people want to help, what do they do?", "qSentId": 613}]